[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Everything to do with one of my very attractive booking team, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "What is the secret of the Morgan Freeman age-defying process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Got to be genes because I don't really do anything else.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Morgan Freeman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "You don't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "ORGAN: Are you vain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Well, I try to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "You played a lady's love interest finally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "What made you crumble?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, it just -- it came my way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Did you like playing a romantic lead finally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "So have you finally performed your first love scene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Kind of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Were you excited by it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I was -- I was stunned.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "So it was a non-scripted assault on your lips?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "It was a non-scripted assault.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Where did it go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Well, we don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Where are we going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "You never actually got to do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Is it a matter of bitter personal regret now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "I wouldn't say that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Have you not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "You've never had an affair with one of your actresses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "How have you resisted the trap, the pleasure perhaps that many of your colleagues have fallen into?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "One of the things I think is I just never need to live the part.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", ":"], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, at the end of the day, you're going to break up --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Would you accept that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "A small-time skirt chaser?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "There is a secret that I'll tell you after the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Go on, what's the secret?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Don't chase women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "They'll chase you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Is that your strategy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Does it work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "It works very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "How do you make yourself known as potentially available?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Just don't do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "And does it ever fail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "They're curious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "So basically, a lifetime of non-drooling has been a successful strategy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Any other tips?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "You need to have a large amount of respect for ladies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "How are you dealing with being a single man again after a long time married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "REEMAN: This has happened before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Is that how this works?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "If you say stallion, that adds a connotation that may not go over that well on family television.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Oh, you come on late at night, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Miss Daisy"]}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "ANDY, ACTRESS: What are you doing there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Oh, I -- I just love a house of pictures, Miss Daisy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mississippi"]}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "RP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Why was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Well, growing up, the segregation in Mississippi just sort of had us all a little upset with the situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "RB", ",", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "What did it motivate you to try and achieve in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Your teachers tell you, get an education and go somewhere, be something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "In the sense that you're a young black man growing up in Mississippi at the time, your chances of getting on in life are pretty close to zero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "If you stayed there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mississippi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Has Obama helped the process of eradicating racism or has it, in a strange way, made it worse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Made it worse.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Does it unnerve you that the Tea Party is gaining such traction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, it just shows the weak, dark underside of America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Are you disappointed that Obama hasn't been more aggressive in taking them on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "REEMAN: Kind of.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "You think so?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Oh, surely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Do you think he has it in him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Of course, he does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "You were protecting him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "He gets you a title fight or did he just bust you out banging your head against other people's fists until you lost your eye?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "RP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I had my shot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 474, "question": "What was the movie before that where you felt most like this is the one, I'm going to get an Oscar for this, and didn't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "\"Driving Miss Daisy.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Did you get to a point when you've made all these movies and you still haven't won one, you start to think, I'm never going to win an Oscar.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "How many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Five.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "You want the truth or you want me to make something up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "The truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "What're you talking about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Can you tell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Did you relate to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Actually, no, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Why was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Well, you have different reasons for that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "And you did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "REEMAN: Well, I like directors that listen to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "\"Shawshank Redemption\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I wouldn't have changed a thing in it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "So did you finally get your way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "But you had to have a battle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I had to have a battle at one point, just to say, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "What will directors think of what you're saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Well, they -- they -- they -- all the good ones understand it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood"]}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "I asked before the break, which is the movie you would make again, not to change, but just to relive the experience for whatever reason if you had a month to live, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "REEMAN: Anything I did with Clint Eastwood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "He's just great to work with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Maybe bring your friend Clint?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Well, that would be interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["10 million dollars"]}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "REEMAN: Well, it's just that watching this young man, this actor, make this transition from I want 10 million dollars for the rest of my life like -- let me you ask you this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Is that -- was that painful to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "It's a state of mind, really, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Did you feel like you'd been unfairly treated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Slightly, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "You're what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "I'm cool.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "But have you been able to have an ongoing relationship, a friendship?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Not at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "No, I don't want it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "You don't want it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "I don't know, I suppose 27 years together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Yes, but, you know, this -- I don't -- there were no kids involved that we have to worry about in that situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "So you never speak to each other at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Well, not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "No, why would it be strange?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "If you don't have that glue, I guess there's no real need to, is there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Do you think you'll get married again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 699, "question": "How do you have the temerity if you don't believe in yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Let's hold the thought that you're God...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Alpha", "Omega"]}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Who are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "I'm the one, the creator of the heavens and the earth, Alpha and Omega.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "Do you like playing God?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Yes, it was fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "But what I mean is that if God exists it only has to -- it can only exist in you, not outside you, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Where do you physically continue, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "If you -- when you die, you feed something that lives.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 765, "question": "And if so, what would they be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 766, "answer": "You know, I don't think you know that until you get there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "What would be the biggest regret of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "What's the one thing you would change if you could go back in time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "I'm not going to tell you that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "How bad is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "Really bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 784, "question": "I mean, in moments like that, do you go through the cliche is there life flash before you kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "No, I didn't even know what was going on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "So it's pretty well a dead hand, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "Pretty much a dead -- a dead hand, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 804, "question": "Does that impact on your acting at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 805, "answer": "Only if I have to do something and pretend that it's not dead.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "Were you left or right handed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "Left.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "So how has that affected your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "Well, conventional wisdom says that left-handed people are much more adaptable if they have to learn to use their right hand than right-handed people, because you live in a right-handed world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 820, "question": "Can you still do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 821, "answer": "Yes, I play golf with one hand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "With one hand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 824, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 825, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 827, "question": "Can you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 828, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 845, "question": "Not what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 846, "answer": "In my right mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 870, "question": "And do you believe from your seafaring that they are more intelligent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 871, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 883, "question": "How was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 884, "answer": "That was great fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 896, "question": "Are you tempted, though, because, I mean, you've got a good voice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 897, "answer": "I'm not even tempted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 906, "question": "Are you going to do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 907, "answer": "If -- if he gets it together, I'm going.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 911, "question": "Have you chosen the song yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 912, "answer": "No, because we haven't decided actually that we're going to do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sinatra"]}, "docId": "111229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 917, "question": "Well, what's your favorite Sinatra song?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 918, "answer": "I don't have a favorite Sinatra song.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sinatra"]}}]